wildlandsfire.com 2014-03-14

# Privacy | LION

LION is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to it when using the LION website. All technical and corporate measures have been put in place to ensure that outside parties do not obtain personally identifiable information about you from our website, nor use it unlawfully.

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit [www.lionprotects.com](http://www.lionprotects.com/ "www.lionprotects.com") and associated pages at the Website.

Typically, LION receives personally identifiable information from its website visitors only when it is provided voluntarily, such as when you elect to provide LION with your email address. We collect, maintain, and use this personal information to contact you and respond to your comments or requests for information.

If you provide LION with your email, we will inform you of updated website features, promotional events, product wear test opportunities and new products, research or services that may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive these emails, you may click on a link at the bottom of the email message to access an opt-out page.

LION also collects information that does not reveal the identity of visitors. This information includes how many visitors log onto our website and what pages they access. We only use this information to help us assess our website and the services offered via the website.

**Data Sharing**

LION will not trade, share, or sell the voluntarily submitted personal information with any third parties without your consent, unless required by law or as disclosed to you when the information is collected.

**Cookies**

Cookies help LION improve your website visit. A cookie is a small file that your web browser places on your computer when you visit a website. This helps us recognize you when you return to our website. We may use such technology to obtain non-personal information from you as an online visitor. To accept cookies, go into your browser preferences and check that cookies are being accepted. You can also turn off the “cookie” function through most standard browsers though that may affect your use of this Website.

When you visit the Website, LION automatically receives and records information from your browser, including your IP Address and the page you request. Site usage information helps us to evaluate how our visitors use and navigate the Website on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors to each web page, and the length of their visits.

By using this Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your use of this Website after any new policy becomes effective means that you agree to all of the terms of the new policy.

LION does not control the privacy policies of our business partners, suppliers or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks.
